<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Wordle</string>

    <string name="play">PLAY</string>
    <string name="how_to_play">HOW TO PLAY</string>
    <string name="settings">SETTINGS</string>

    <string name="android_word">Android</string>

    <string name="game_mode">GAME MODE</string>
    <string name="classic">CLASSIC</string>
    <string name="classic_description">This mode follows the traditional Wordle format where players have attempts depending on difficulty to guess the hidden word correctly.
        Each correct guess reveals the position of the letters in the word with color-coding.</string>
    <string name="infinite">INFINITE</string>
    <string name="infinite_description">In this mode, players can keep guessing words continuously until they do not succeed.
        Score is accumulated with each correct guess, and theres no limit to the number of words you can guess</string>
    <string name="number">NUMBER</string>
    <string name="number_description">Similar to Classic Wordle, but without color-highlighted letters.
        Instead, players receive feedback in the form of the number of letters guessed correctly and the number of those letters correctly positioned.</string>

    <string name="difficulty">DIFFICULTY</string>
    <string name="normal">NORMAL</string>
    <string name="normal_description">Players have six rows to guess the word, similar to the Classic setup.
        This mode provides a balanced challenge suitable for most players.</string>
    <string name="hard">HARD</string>
    <string name="hard_description">With only five rows available for guessing, Hard mode increases the challenge by reducing the number of attempts.
        Players need to be more strategic and accurate with their guesses to succeed.</string>
    <string name="extreme">EXTREME</string>
    <string name="extreme_description">Extreme mode offers the toughest challenge with only four rows for guessing.
        It demands precision and careful deduction as players have fewer attempts to decipher the hidden word.</string>
    <string name="start_game">START GAME</string>
</resources>
